Inventory of the G. Walter Mapp Papers 1895-1935
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
G. Walter Mapp Papers, 1895-1935.
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Mss. 84 M32
10,139 items.
Papers, 1895-1935, of George Walter Mapp consisting chiefly of his personal and professional correspondence. Topics in the correspondence include women suffrage, Prohibition, 1918 First District of Virginia Congressional Democratic primary, 1928 presidential election, and the 1929 Virginia gubernatorial Democratic primary.
Schuyler Otis Bland,; Harry Flood Byrd,; James Cannon,; Julian Alvin Carroll Chandler,; Adéle Clark,; George Preston Coleman,; Mary Haldane Coleman,; G. Walter Mapp,; Thomas Staples Martin,; Lucy Randolph Mason,; Robert Walton Moore,; John Garland Pollard,; Claude Augustus Swanson,; Elbert Lee Trinkle,; Lyon Gardiner Tyler,; Lila Meade Valentine.
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
Acc. no. 84-17; Gift: 9,988 items, 1984.
Acc. no. 1994.88; Gift: ca. 150 items, 1994.
Acc. no. 1995.50; Gift: 1 item, 1995.
Biographical/Historical Information
George Walter Mapp was born on 25 May 1873 to parents, Dr. John E. Mapp and Margaret Benson (LeCato) Mapp. In 1891, he received a degree of licentiate from the College of William and Mary. This qualified him to teach at the college while studying for a bachelor of arts degree. Upon graduation, he taught at Hagsett Military Academy in Danville, Kentucky. While at Hagsett, he attended classes at Centre College, Kentucky, graduating with a law degree in 1897.
Following graduation Mapp practiced law on the Eastern Shore of Virginia. He entered into several partnerships, the first alongside his cousin Otho F. Mears. Upon its dissolution, he formed a partnership with his brother J. Brooks Mapp, which included an associate, Mr. Herbert Barnes.
Mapp served in the Virginia State Senate from 1911 to 1923 representing the thirty- seventh district, which encompassed Accomac, Northampton, and Princess Anne counties. As a Democratic politician, he was a leader in the temperance movement and fought for women's suffrage. Mapp ran unsuccessfully for Congress in 1918 and for governor in 1925 and 1929.
In his later years, he served as the chairman of the State Commission of Fisheries and on the Board of Visitors at the College of William and Mary.
G. Walter Mapp married Miss Georgia Richardson Quinby on 10 November 1900. She died within a year. On 9 November 1910, he remarried Miss Mildred Townsend Aydelotte. The couple had two children. Mapp died in 1941.
Scope and Content Information
Papers, 1895-1935, of George Walter Mapp consisting chiefly his of personal and professional correspondence. Topics in the correspondence include women suffrage, Prohibition, 1918 First District of Virginia Congressional Democratic primary, 1928 presidential election, and the 1929 Virginia gubernatorial Democratic primary. In addition to papers pertaining to Mapp's political career, much of the collection pertains to Mapp's legal practice on the Eastern Shore of Virginia and includes supporting notes and documents referring to specific cases. There are pamphlets, speeches and newspaper clippings covering his political career from 1911 to 1929.
Prominent correspondents include S. O. Bland, Harry Flood Byrd, James Cannon, J. A. C. (Julian Alvin Carroll) Chandler, Adele Clark, George Preston Coleman, Mary Haldane Coleman, Thomas S. (Thomas Staples) Martin, Lucy Randolph Mason, R. Walton (Robert Walton) Moore, John Garland Pollard, Claude A. Swanson, E. Lee (Elbert Lee) Trinkle, Lyon G. Tyler and Lila Meade Valentine.
The collection also includes correspondence of Mapp's law partner, Herbert Barnes.
Arrangement
Organization
This collection is arranged into 7 series. Series 1 contains correspondence of G. Walter Mapp; Series 2 contains correspondence of Herbert Barnes; Series 3 contains political papers; Series 4 contains legal and/or business papers; Series 5 contains books, other printed material, and artifacts; Series 6 contains addition 1994.88; and Series 7 contains addition 1995.50.
Arrangement
This collection is primarily arranged alphabetically either by correspondent's last name or by county name.
Additional Descriptive Data
Bibliography
Hohner, Robert A. Prohibition and politics: the life of Bishop James Cannon, Jr.Columbia, S.C.: University of South Carolina Press, c1999.
Swem Library, College of William and Mary.
Call Number: BX8495 .C245 H64 1999
Related Materials
See also G. Walter Mapp Faculty/Alumni File, University Archives, Swem Library, College of William and Mary.
Index Terms
Persons:
Bland, Schuyler Otis, 1872- 1950.; Byrd, Harry Flood, 1887-1966.; Cannon, James, 1864-1944.; Chandler, J. A. C. (Julian Alvin Carroll), 1872-1934.; Clark, Adéle, 1882-1983.; Coleman, George Preston, 1870-1948.; Coleman, Mary Haldane.; Martin, Thomas S. (Thomas Staples), 1847-1919.; Mason, Lucy Randolph, 1882-1959.; Moore, R. Walton (Robert Walton), 1859- 1941.; Pollard, John Garland, 1871-1937.; Swanson, Claude Augustus, 1862-1939.; Trinkle, E. Lee (Elbert Lee), 1876-1939.; Tyler, Lyon Gardiner, 1853-1935.; Valentine, Lila Meade, 1865- 1921.
Subjects:
Prohibition-- Virginia.; Virginia--Politics and government.
Occupations:
Practice of law--Virginia--History.; Lawyers--Virginia-- Correspondence.
Components List
  Series 1: Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp
- Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp, 1895-1935. (Box 1-8)
  Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp.
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent's last name.
  - General Correspondence, 1895-1935. (Box 1-7)
    - General Correspondence: A-Ca, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 1:1-265)
      - Duplicate correspondence with Mr. James Abbot, Mappsville, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:1)
      - Duplicate correspondence with The Accomack News,1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:2)
      - Correspondence from A. Johnston Ackiss, lawyer, Norfolk, Virginia, 1911, 1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:3)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with L. M. Acree, grocer, Gordonsville, Virginia, October 1928., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:4)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Berkley D. Adams, Charlotte County, Virginia, Mapp's 1929 state gubernatorial campaign manager, April-December 1929., 18 items. (Box-folder 1:5)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. E. Adams, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1918-1929., 7 items. (Box-folder 1:6)
      - Correspondence from George P. Adams, President, Blackstone College for Girls, Blackstone, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:7)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. Pearl R. Adams, Harborton, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:8)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Samuel L. Adams, delegate from Halifax County, Virginia, 1921-1928., 20 items. (Box-folder 1:9)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George W. Addison, Cashville, Virginia, [1911?]., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:10)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with the E. S. Adkins and Company, Salisbury, Maryland, 1906-1935., 9 items. (Box-folder 1:11)
      - Correspondence from H. P. Kjerschow Agersborg, biology professor, Atlantic University, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:12)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Ida N. Ailworth, Baltimore, Maryland, 1932-1933., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:13)
      - Correspondence from Cynthia Westover Alden, President-General of the International Sunshine Society, 1920., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:14)
      - Correspondence from Edwin A. Alderman, President of the University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:15)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Raymond Pace Alexander, lawyer, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:16)
      - Duplicate correspondence to S. W. Alexander, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:17)
      - Correspondence from Florence E. Allen, lawyer, Cleveland, Ohio, 1917., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:18)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Howard Allen, in the County Jail, Accomac, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:19)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. H. Allen, New York City, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:20)
      - Correspondence from William H. Allen, Dover, Delaware, 1899., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:21)
      - Correspondence from the Aluminum Cooking Utensil County, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:22)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with L. P. Allyn, Harborton, Virginia, 1912., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:23)
      - Correspondence from Lora H. Allyson, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:24)
      - Correspondence from the American Credit Association, 1911., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:25)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the American Surety Company, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:26)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with the American Typewriter Exchange, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:27)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William B. Ames, Norfolk, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:28)
      - Duplicate correspondence to S. K. Ames, Baltimore, Maryland, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:29)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Stanley D. Ames, cashier, Eastern Shore Banking Company, Keller, Virginia, 1933-1934., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:30)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Warner Ames, lawyer, Ononcock, Virginia, 1906-1934., 7 items. (Box-folder 1:31)
      - Correspondence from J. C. Amory, Parksley, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:32)
      - Correspondence from Dr. Anderson, St. Martins, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:33)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Bessle B. Anderson, Nassawadox, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:34)
      - Correspondence from E. L. Anderson, Wardtown, Virginia, 1909, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:35)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. C. Anderson, New York, New York, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:36)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John L. Anderton, Chincoteague, Virginia, ca. 1910., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:37)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John T. Anderton, Tangier, Virginia and Crisfield, Maryland, 1912-1924., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:38)
      - Correspondence from T. F. Anderton, Gloucester Point, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:39)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Edward Andrews, Roanoke, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:40)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mr. and Mrs. W.L. Andrews, State Senator, Roanoke, Virginia, 1922-1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:41)
      - Correspondence from John H. Annis, Camden, New Jersey, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:42)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Anti-Saloon League of Virginia, 1917., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:43)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Martin W. Ardis, Greenbackville, Virginia, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:44)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Colonel George A. Armes, Washington, D.C., n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:45)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. W. F. Armsworthy, Burgess Store, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:46)
      - Duplicate correspondence to T. M. Arnst, Hague, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:47)
      - Correspondence from Landers Artis, State Farm, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:48)
      - Correspondence from Mary M. Arnice (?), Franklin City, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:49)
      - Correspondence from W. P. Ashburn, Norfolk, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:50)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. T. Ashe, Gloucester, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:51)
      - Duplicate correspondence from F. O. Atha, Baltimore, Maryland, 1905., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:52)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mr. and Mrs. Thomas H. and Melanie Parker Atherton, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, ca. 1911., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:53)
      - Duplicate correspondence to N. W. Atkinson, Richmond, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:54)
      - Correspondence to the Auditor of Public Accounts, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:55)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Axton-Fisher Tobacco Company, Louisville, Kentucky, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:56)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James Aydelotte, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1912-1922., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:57)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John S. Aydelotte, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:58)
      - Correspondence from P. H. Aylett, Accomac, Virginia, 1912., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:59)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with B. Drummond Ayres, delegate from Accomac County, Virginia, 1928-1935., 10 items. (Box-folder 1:60)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Miss Sue Ayres, Hopewell, Virginia, 1926., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:61)
      - Correspondence from W. S. Ayres, Tasley, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:62A)
      - Duplicate correspondence from Ayres and Tyler, Merchandise Brokers, Sioux City, Iowa, 1903., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:62B)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with B. B. Bagby, West Point, Virginia, 1921., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:63)
      - Correspondence from W. P. Bagwell, Blackstone, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:64)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Judges Bailey and Duer, Princess Anne, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:65)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. and Mrs. Norman J. Bailey, Valley Park, Missouri, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:66)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. J. Baley, Tangier, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:67)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Frank L. Ball, Clarendon, Virginia, 1921-1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:68)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Richard Ball, Hallwood, Virginia, ca. 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:69)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Rev. H. P. Baker, Roanoke, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:70)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Bruce C. Banks, 1934., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:71)
      - Duplicate correspondence from H. P. Bannon, Accomac, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:72)
      - Correspondence from Henry G. Barbee, Norfolk, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:73)
      - Correspondence from Robert S. Barbour, South Boston, Virginia, 1914 and 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:74)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James B. Barker, Richmond, Virginia, 1930-1931., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:75)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. E. Barker, Gate City, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:76)
      - Duplicate correspondence from Mr. Barlow, Pennington Gap, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:77)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Eugene W. Barnes, Gargatha, Virginia, 1911-1935., 16 items. (Box-folder 1:78)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Forrest Barnes, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:79)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Herbert Barnes, law partner of Mapp and Mapp, Accomac, Virginia, 1922-1925., 16 items. (Box-folder 1:80)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Herbert Barnes, 1929-1933., 18 items. (Box-folder 1:81)
      - Duplicate correspondence to James Daniel Barnes, Accomac, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:82)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Ralph Forrest Barnes, Gargatha, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:83)
      - Correspondence from Thomas J. Barnes, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:84)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. C. L. Barret, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:85A)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Jane Porter Barrett, Peak Turnout, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:85B)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. E. Barrow, Richmond, Virginia, 1927-1928., 6 items. (Box-folder 1:86)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Madeline L. Barrow, Farmville, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:87)
      - Correspondence from Robert T. Barton, Jr., Richmond, Virginia, 1935., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:88)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. O. Baum, Princess Anne County, Virginia, 1922, 1927., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:89)
      - Correspondence from G. Gordon Battle, New York, 1930., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:90)
      - Correspondence from Bessie Battaile, Sassafras, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:91)
      - Correspondence from Thomas J. Bayley, Onancock, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:92)
      - Correspondence from Sadie P. Bayly, Accomac, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:93)
      - Duplicate correspondence to B. C. A., Baltimore, Maryland, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:94)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George Beach, Pungoteague, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:95)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John L. Beale, Hague, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:96)
      - Correspondence from Richard L. Beale, Bowling Green, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:97)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James A. Bear, Roanoke, Virginia, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:98)
      - Correspondence from J. D. Beasley, Grangeville, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:99)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. L. Beauchamp, Baltimore, Maryland, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:100)
      - Duplicate correspondence to F. C. Bedinger, Boydton, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:101)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Beecher and Barr, Pottsville, Pennsylvania, 1906., 8 items. (Box-folder 1:102)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Bell Book and Stationary Company, Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:103)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. C. Bell, Franktown, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:104)
      - Correspondence from Frank B. Bell, Machipongo, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:105)
      - Duplicate correspondence to G. W. Bell, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:106)
      - Correspondence from T. P. Bell, Machipongo, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:107)
      - Correspondence from Joseph Bellows, Ocran, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:108)
      - Correspondence from J. D. Belote, Melfa, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:109)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. Norman Belote, Onancock, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:110)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Walter A. Belote, Melfa, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:111)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Henry R. Bennett, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:112)
      - Correspondence from Howard S. Bennett, MCV, Richmond, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:113)
      - Correspondence from Leonard Bennett, Hack's Neck, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:114)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Capt. C. C. Berkley, Newport News, Virginia, 1920, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:115)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Berlin Building and Loan Association, 1931-1935., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:116)
      - Correspondence from Bernard [?], with the American Expeditionary Forces, France, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:117)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Albert Berry, Washington, D.C., 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:118)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Gladys Berry, Washington, D.C., 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:119)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Biltmore Industries, Asheville, North Carolina, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:120)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Aubrey W. Binns, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:121)
      - Correspondence from Charles H. Birch, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:122)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Iona Birch, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:123)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Nelly Bird, Richmond, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:124)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Thomas W. Blackstone, Accomac, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:125)
      - Correspondence from R. E. Blackell, Randolph-Macon College, Ashland, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:126)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Leonora G. Blake, 1931., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:127)
      - Correspondence with S. O. Bland, 1st District Congressman, Newport News, Virginia, 1918-1935., 62 items. (Box-folder 1:128-131)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. O. Bland, 1918-1926., 14 items. (Box-folder 1:128)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. O. Bland, 1927-1933., 25 items. (Box-folder 1:129)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. O. Bland, 1934., 14 items. (Box-folder 1:130)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. O. Bland, 1935., 9 items. (Box-folder 1:131)
      - Correspondence from Louis Bloomberg, Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:132)
      - Correspondence from C. F. Bloxom, Bloxom, Virginia, 1909., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:133)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with O. A. Bloxom, Newport News, Virginia, 1918-1932., 10 items. (Box-folder 1:134)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. L. (Dick) Bloxom, Bloxom, Virginia, 1924-1931., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:135)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Woodrum Bloxom, Grotons, Virginia, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:136)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Esther Blum, Norfolk, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:137)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. C. Boatwright, Jonesville, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:138A)
      - Correspondence from R. J. and Joseph C. Boggs, Nandua, Virginia, 1898-1900, 1912., 11 items. (Box-folder 1:138B)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. C. Bond, Accomac, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:139)
      - Correspondence from Miriam Boocock, Keswick, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:140)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George E. Booker, Richmond, Virginia, 1925, 1930., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:141)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Marshall Booker, Halifax Court House, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:142)
      - Telegram from Booth's Drug Store, Danville, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:143)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William Harris Booth, Ruark, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:144)
      - Correspondence from [?] Booth, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:145)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John T. Borum, Onancock, Virginia, 1925-1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:146)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. W. Borum, Norfolk, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:147)
      - Box-Folder 1:148 currently does not exist in this collection.
      - Box-Folder 1:149 currently does not exist in this collection.
      - Duplicate correspondence to John D. Bosman, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:150)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Alfred C. Bossom, New York, 1920., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:151)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Davis Bottom, Richmond, Virginia, 1926, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:152)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Carey Ben Bow, Bluefield, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:153)
      - Correspondence from R. T. Bowden, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:154)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. W. Bowdoin, Bloxom, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:155)
      - Correspondence from Bruce Bowe, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:156)